Kevin Sierra Castro

Cartagena, Colombia· <u>linkedin.com/in/kevin-sierra-castro</u>· +57 301 7847680· kevnsc18@gmail.com

I am a systems engineering student with a profile oriented towards software development. I have experience in creating web and mobile applications using modern technologies such as React Native, NestJS and PostgreSQL. Focused on continuous improvement and collaboration in agile teams. I look for opportunities to apply my skills and contribute to the success of innovative projects.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Corporación Universitaria Rafael Nuñez

Cartagena, Colombia

Junior FrontEnd Developer

August 2023–December 2023

- Development of a new interface for the university website using Javascript, PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS and Joomla
- Collaboration with teams that use the agile Scrum methodology
- Improve site usability, increase optimization and security

AgilCurn (Independent Project)

Cartagena, Colombia

FullStack Developer

February 2024-Current

- Development of a mobile application for project management of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) using the Scrum methodology.
- Technologies used include React Native, Expo, NestJs, TypeScript, PostgreSQL, Prisma, JWT, Nodemailer, Socket.io
- Implementation of an interactive kanban board to visualize workflows, user registration and authentication system, and a real-time chat

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- FrontEnd: React, React native(Expo), JavaScript, Typescript, Tailwind CSS
- BackEnd: Next.js, NestJs, Node.js, PostgreSQL
- **Version Control:** Git(GitHub)
- Tools and Technologies: JWT, Nodemailer, Socket.io, Joomla, Redux Toolkit

EDUCATION

Corporación Universitaria Rafael Nuñez

Technology in the development of information systems and software

Cartagena, Colombia

February 2021-Decembre

2023

Corporación Universitaria Rafael Nuñez

Systems engineer

Cartagena, Colombia

February 2024-Current

CERTIFICATIONS

- FrontEnd Developer (React) HackerRank
- <u>JavaScript (Intermediate) HackerRank</u>

LANGUAGES

• Spanish: Native

• English: Intermediate

• Italian: Intermediate

REFERENCES

José Eduardo Sierra Vargas

FullStack Software Developer

Companies: EPAM - Dualboot Partners **LinkedIn:** <u>linkedin.com/in/jose-sierra</u>